孩子们, 在交往过程中要不断地...
Kids, one of the things you learn about relationships is that you're never done
去了解对方
getting to know someone.
每个人都有秘密
Everyone has secrets.
有些是好的
Some are nice.
你知道怎么烤薄饼么?
You know how to make crepes?
真有你的
That is so cool.
有些是不好的
Some aren't as nice.
然后就是和德雷克交往 算上你
And then there was Derek, and counting you,
- 一共是... - 我知道有多少人了
- that puts the total up to-- - Oh, I got your total.
我一直在算
I've been counting along.
还有一些就是惊悚的了
And some are just weird.
你害怕七个小矮人?
You're scared of the seven dwarfs?
就怕多克!事情很蹊跷 (小矮人的头领)
Just Doc. He's creepy.
你看他就读的是医学院
I mean the guy went to medical school.
但为什么和6个煤炭工人住一起?
What's he doing living with six coal miners?
同志们 我兴奋地一晚上都没睡觉
Oh, man! I'm so excited. I couldn't sleep last night.
- 我打赌你们也没睡着 - 为什么?
- I bet you guys couldn't either. - Why?
当然是因为夏普形象店 第500家分店的
Only the Gala event for the Grand Opening
盛大开业典礼了 你们都没收到我的邮件?
of Sharper Image's 500th store. Didn't you get my email?
在你第四次发 猴子闻自己屁股的视频时
No, I blocked your address after the fourth time
我就把你拖进黑名单了
you sent me the video of the monkey sniffing his own butt.
我请客 我给你们准备了3张足疗卡
Come on! It's on me. I'm buying three of you foot massagers
和一套鼻毛修建工具 别乐得忘了自己姓啥哦
and one of you a nose hair trimmer. You know who you are.
来 开路
Come on, let's go.
好的 走吧
Okay, I'm in.
- 杀向威乐布鲁克商场! - 杀向威乐布鲁克商场
- To the Willowbrook Mall! - To the Willowbrook Mall.
在商场?  那我不去了
Oh, it's at a mall? I'm not going.
什么?  为什么啊?
What? Why not?
我就是不喜欢去商场
I just don't feel like going to a mall.
我们可以分肉桂面包的
We can split a Cinnabon.
不  我真的不去了
No, I'm really not going to go.
- 来吧 那很有意思的 - 我说了不去!
- Come on, it'll be fun. - No, I don't go to malls!
抱歉 我真的很不喜欢商场
Sorry, I just don't like malls.
为什么不喜欢?
Why not?
我不太想说
I'd rather not say.
- 夏普形象店 - 那里有时装展的
- Sharper Images. - But that's where clothes live.
算了 伙计们 罗宾不喜欢商场
Guys, guys, guys, Robin doesn't like malls.
如果她不想说原因 那就不要勉强了
If she doesn't want to tell us why, she doesn't have to.
我想我们应该尊重她的隐私
I think we should all just respect her privacy.
谢谢你 泰德
Thanks, Ted.
你到底为什么不愿去商场啊?
So, what's the deal with you and malls?
你不是说过么 如果我不想说
I thought you said that, if I didn't want to talk about it,
我就不用说了
I didn't have to.
那是当着别人的面
Yeah, with those people.
但我是你男朋友啊 到底怎么回事?
But I'm your boyfriend. Come on. What is it?
难道你在商场里被逮捕过?
Did you get arrested at a mall?
没
No.
- 在商场里被甩过? - 泰德
- Dumped at a mall? - Ted.
在商场里被认出来是加拿大人了?
Found out you were Canadian at a mall?
够了吧
Let it go.
困在商场的假山下面?
Trapped under a fake boulder at a mall?
- 别说笑了 - 在商场里被骚扰过?
- Let it go. - Mauled at the mall?
够了!
Let it go!
谁能困在商场的假山下?
And who gets trapped under a fake boulder at the mall?
我9岁时掉进过 在俄亥俄州 不骗你
Not me in Ohio when I was nine, that's for sure.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第九集
翻译：    胖丫头    校对：     雨亦奇
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
我不能理解 为什么罗宾 不愿告诉我  她讨厌商场的原因?
I don't get it. Why won't Robin tell me why she hates malls?
泰德  你应该感到庆幸罗宾有秘密
Ted, you should be happy Robin has a secret.
你对一个人了解的越多
The more you learn about a person,
你就越逼近"终结时刻"
the better chance you have of hitting the fatal "Oh" moment.
"终结时刻"?
The "Oh" moment?
就是当你知道了 对方的某个事情后
Yeah, that moment when you find out that one detail about a person
你们的关系就终结了
that is going to be a deal breaker.
这是一个承诺戒指
It's a promise ring.
我向上帝承诺结婚前 我会一直保持处女之身
I made a pact with God to stay a virgin till I'm married.
我才不会乱节食
I don't have an eating disorder.
我都把食物放进嘴里 咀嚼后再吐出来
It's just when I put food in my mouth, I chew it, and then I spit it out.
我马上30岁了
I just turned 30.
所以相信我 关于对方的事
So trust me, you want to postpone
你知道的越晚越好
knowing anything about each other for as long as possible.
这我不同意 就算有所谓的"终结时刻"
Mmm. I disagree. If there is some potential "Oh" moment,
我也想尽快知道 这样... 还能有回旋的余地
I want to know about it right away. I mean, what's the alternative?
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you, man and wife.
我爱你
I love you.
我是个变性人
I used to be a dude.
我同意泰德的观点
Yeah,  I agree with Ted.
在真正的交往中  应该无所保留
In a real relationship, you share everything.
所以我和马修之间 从来不保留秘密
That's why Marshall and I don't keep any secrets.
你真是个天真的小孩 这有枚硬币...
You are such a cutie pie. Here's a quarter.
去自动点唱机唱首歌玩
Go play a song on the jukebox.
他们说的是真的 他们把所有事都告诉对方了
No, it's true. They tell each other everything.
我能抖出一箩筐事 那是马修绝对不可能告诉你的
I can think of tons of things, there's no way Marshall's told you.
那你来试试
Try me.
你知道马修在 切尔敦有过什么事么?
Do you know about the time Marshall was in Trenton?
有头驴扒掉了他的裤子
Donkey ate his pants. Yup.
在孟菲斯比尔的单身汉聚会上呢?
Bill's bachelor party in Memphis?
就是那次大家不得不用 泵把他胃里的镍币吸出来的时候?
Oh, when they had to pump out all the nickels from his stomach?
你真可以...在西雅图?
Wow. Okay. Seattle.
少蒙人了! 马修从没去过西海岸
Trick question. Marshall's never been to the Pacific Northwest
因为他害怕雪怪
because he's afraid of Sasquatch.
该死 你都对了
Damn, you're good.
我不是害怕雪怪 而是我觉得应该随时保持警惕
I'm not afraid of Sasquatch, I just think we should all be on alert.
相信我 他们不仅知道对方的事
Trust me. Not only do they tell each other everything,
他们什么八卦都不放过
they want to know everything.
淋浴后我开始刷牙 但突然想起...
So after the shower I was brushing my teeth. And I was like,
天哪   我本打算来点橘子汁的
"Oh, man! I wanted to have some orange juice.
应该先喝了再刷牙
I should have done that first."
但我已经把牙膏挤在牙刷上了
But I already had the toothpaste on the toothbrush.
所以我就不管了 先刷了再说...
So I just went ahead and brushed them anyway.
接下来怎么样了?
What happened next?
但同时 罗宾却什么都不跟我说
Yeah, meanwhile, Robin tells me nothing.
那你想知道罗宾的秘密么?
Fine. Do you want to know what Robin's secret is?
你知道?
You know?
当然
Of course I know.
她不敢正眼 瞧咱们并且脸颊绯红
She couldn't look at us, her face got flushed--
她觉得难以启齿了
that's shame, my friend.
我们的罗宾曾经是色情...
Our friend Robin used to do porn, wait for it...
行业工作者
...ography.
你用不着这么玩大喘气的
Yeah, we didn't really need to wait for that.
而且这太荒唐了
And it's ridiculous.
这不好说 他说的也有可能
I don't know. He could be right.
她发出过假的叫床声
She does have the fake orgasm noises down.
说什么呢
Hey!
怎么了? 墙的隔音效果又不好
What? The walls are thin.
我说的不是这个!
That's not what I'm "hey"ing you about.
你有没有考虑过这种可能
You know what it might be?
听上去有些夸张 但是也许罗宾已经结婚了
This is going to sound a little crazy but what if Robin is married?
结婚? 那和商场有什么关系?
Married? What does that have to do with the mall?
也许她是在商场结的婚
Well, maybe she got married at the mall.
在我老家明尼苏达州 很多人都想把婚礼办在
Back home in Minnesota, a ton of people get married
商场 那里很棒的
at the Mall of America. It's great.
有华丽的用来拍电影的 室内高尔夫球场
There's this gorgeous indoor golf course for pictures,
眼花缭乱的美食 是结婚地点的最佳...
numerous fine dining options, and talk about a reasonable--
- 我们不要在商场结婚! - 我只是假设一下
- We are not getting married at the mall! - Well, just meet with the guy.
她没结婚  她厌恶结婚的
She's not married. Robin hates marriage.
那是因为她已经在商场
Because she already got married.
结婚了
At the mall.
罗宾在来到纽约前...
No, because before Robin moved to New York, she...
到底是干什么的啊?
What was she doing?
我不知道 我每次提到在加拿大的事
Well, I don't know. Whenever I ask her about Canada,
她就沉默了
she kind of clams up.
她真是一个注重隐私的人
She's a pretty private person.
除了在谈到...
Except when she's talking about...
我有一个朋友结婚很早
Oh, a friend of mine in Canada got married way too young
结果使她很厌恶结婚
and it really turned her off to marriage.
你认为这个结婚蛋糕怎么样?
What  do you think of this wedding cake?
不错 我喜欢
Oh, I like it.
你记得我提过的 一个在加拿大的朋友
Hey, you remember that friend of mine in Canada
就是结婚太早的那个?
who got married way too young?
她的结婚时就是 菲尔茨太太做的巨型蛋糕
Her wedding cake was a Mrs. Fields' giant cookie.
我可不要...
No.
我那个在加拿大结婚太早的朋友
My friend in Canada who got married way too young,
她的婚誓发了两次 一次是用法语发的
they had to do their vows twice, once in French.
加拿大人也讲法语么?
They speak French there, too?
加拿大以前是法国的殖民地,当地人有很多都是用法语作为母语的
什么乱七八糟的事
God, that place is a mess.
所以你认为她在加拿大 并没有这个所谓的朋友?
So you don't think there's any "friend" from Canada?
肯定是的
Oh, I'm sure there is.
我有个朋友到10岁了  还尿床呢
Just like I have a "friend" who wet his bed till he was ten.
动动你的脑子吧  泰德
Use your brain, Ted.
伙计们 罗宾不可能结婚了
Guys, there's no way Robin is married.
这种猜测忒荒唐了点
It's ludicrous to even suggest it.
- 就是的 巴尼 - 她肯定是干色情行业的
- Thank you, Barney. - 'Cause it's porn.
我再去要杯啤酒
I need another beer.
罗宾肯定不是干那个的 我跟你打赌 罗宾肯定是结婚了
Robin was not in porn. I bet you anything that she's married.
打赌两万美金
$20,000 says it's porn.
我没两万美金
I don't have $20,000.
那你有点什么?
Well, then what do you have?
- 能借... - 别想
- Well... - No.
我知道了  换个形式
I've got it. The ultimate wager--
打赌输了 打耳光
slap bet.
打耳光? 我们小时候这么干过
Oh, slap bet. We used to do those when I was a kid.
打赌打耳光是什么意思?
What the hell's a slap bet?
打赌赢了的人可以打 输了的人力度不限
Whoever is right gets to slap the other person in the face
而且输了的人不许还击
as hard as they possibly can-- but no rings.
你真的要这么干? 这太幼稚了吧
Are you really going to do that? That's so immature.
- 你当这次赌的监察官 - 我干...我的权力是什么?
- You can be Slap Bet Commissioner. - Ooh, I love it. What are my powers?
如果出现争议由你来仲裁
Um, if a problem arises and we need a ruling, that's your job.
但是你不得有私心
But you have to be unbiased
要保证这个赌公平公正公开
and put the integrity of slap bet above all else.
这可是件让你祖坟上冒青烟的事
This is an honor you will take with you to your grave.
等你百年之后 墓碑上会这么刻着
On your tombstone, it will read,
莉莉・艾得仁  不仅是 一位体贴的妻子 可爱的朋友
"Lily Aldrin, caring wife, loving friend,
还是打耳光游戏的监察官
Slap Bet Commissioner."
那么你的墓碑上会刻着 "牺牲于马修的猛掌袭击下"
And your tombstone will read "Got slapped by Marshall, so hard he died."
继续来 我要怎样在罗宾面前 切入到"丈夫"这个话题上
Okay. What if I just ask Robin point blank if she has a husband?
你不是说尊重罗宾的隐私嘛
You said you would respect her privacy,
你还是不要计较这件事了
so maybe you should just drop it.
算了 就这么着吧
Yeah, you're right.
老工
Husband.
你的"老公"拼错了
There's no "P" in husband.
你对这个挺有研究的啊
Wow, you seem to know a lot about husbands.
好吧 我改
Fine. I'll take it back.
你既然提到了"老公" 给你讲个有意思的事
Oh, hey, since you mentioned husbands, this is great, you're going to love this.
知道马修吧 他认为你那天
Marshall, you know Marshall. He thinks that the reason
不愿意去商场的原因
you didn't want to go to the mall the other day
你在加拿大时已经结婚 婚礼是在商场办的
is because you got married at a mall and have a husband in Canada.
我说他有病 你说他是不是?
I told him he's crazy. Because he's crazy, right?
真不知他哪根筋搭错了
I mean, how crazy is that?
你是想问我结婚没有吧
Are you asking me if I'm married?
你可以问我的
Well, you can ask me.
我当然没结 该你了
Nope, I'm not married. Your turn.
不是说尊重我的隐私么?
What happened to respecting my privacy?
说"不 我没结婚"就好了呗
Look, just say, "No, I'm not married."
泰德 我不明白你为什么...
Ted,  I don't understand why you can't--
就说一句"不 我没结婚"
Just say, "No, I'm not married."
不行
I can't.
马修说的没错
Marshall's right.
我年纪很轻时就结婚了
I was young and I got married.
但这是个错误  他早就离开了...
It was a mistake and he moved away, but...
是的  我结过婚
yeah. I'm married.
你有老公了?
You have a husband?
我当时太年轻 太傻了
I was young and stupid
我们在商场里结婚 并在商场里分手了
and we got married at a mall and we broke up at a mall
从那以后我再也不去商场了
and I... I haven't been to a mall since.
那你怎么没离婚?
Why didn't you get divorced?
他搬到香港工作了 然后我就...
He moved to Hong Kong for work and I was like...
就这么多了
eh, good enough.
就这样了? 这怎么行
Good  enough? That's not good enough.
你还得烤薄饼 弄点瓦夫饼干 这样才行
You order pancakes, you get waffles, that's good enough.
我已经很多年没见过他了
Look, I haven't seen him in years.
这只是我生活里 需要遗忘的一部分
It's just a part of my life I want to forget.
别告诉其他人这件事
Just please don't tell anyone about this.
知道了
Okay.
好家伙 你的手是熊掌啊
Dude, your hand is monstrous.
你以为我是什么? 你不是见识过我的能力了么
Yeah, well, what'd you expect? You've seen my penis.
没想到你会 告诉我们罗宾的秘密
I can't believe you told us Robin's secret.
怎么了?这事你叫我怎么保持沉默?
What? How could I keep something like that to myself?
你不是央求我说的么?
And you begged me to tell you.
有么?
No, I didn't.
告诉我们吧 就说一下嘛 求你了
Please tell us. Just tell us. I'm begging you.
说一下 说一下 就说一下 拜托了...
Tell us. Tell us. Tell us. Please please please--
够了 罗宾她结婚了
Fine. Robin's married.
其实你不该告诉我们的
Yeah, well, you still shouldn't have told us.
你怎么能这么当男友啊?
I mean, what kind of boyfriend are you?
可事实上我根本不是她男朋友
See that's just it, I'm not the boyfriend.
我只是个情妇
I'm the mistress.
不  还不如这
No, not the mistress.
是情夫
The mastress.
情父  这字怎么写来着?
The master. What do you call it?
我肯定是写成情妇
Uh, pretty sure we're going to call it mistress.
我该怎么办? 我的女友是已婚的
What am I going to do? My girlfriend's married.
我该要求她离婚么?
Do I ask her to get a divorce?
泰德 就算她结婚了 那也是个加拿大式婚姻
Ted, even if she is married, it's a Canadian marriage.
好比金钱啊  军队啊 这些身外之物
It's like their money, or their army.
没人在意的
Nobody takes it seriously.
可我在意
It's serious to me.
在一些国家当夫妻分居达5年以上
You know what, in some countries, if you been separated
在法律上  这个婚姻就无效了
for longer than five years, technically, you're no longer married.
这是我在学校 查阅法律书籍知道的
I can check it out at the law library at school.
你的脸上还印着我的指印
I can see my hand print on your face.
别得意的太早
Don't get too cocky, Slappy.
我还在搜集加拿大的色情业资料
I just got a shipment of porn from Canada I have to go through.
这赌我都赢了 你还折腾个什么劲啊?
I won the bet. Why are you still searching?
就算你是对的 也不意味着我是错的
Just because you were right doesn't mean I'm wrong.
算了吧 你只是 在给自己找个理由看色情片
Oh, right, like you need an excuse to watch porn.
加拿大情色片
Canadian porn.
相信我　加拿大的医疗保险
Trust me when I tell you their universal health care system
是不给隆胸买单的
doesn't cover breast implants.
如果我在看到一个平胸的 新斯科瓦省的女人
If I have to sit through one more flat-chested Nova Scotian
骑着马在铺冰机上面溜达的时候
riding a Mountie on the back of a Zamboni
我会崩溃的
I'll go out of my mind.
- 好啊 - 来了
- Hey. - Hey.
我有事跟你说
Listen, dude, I got to talk to you,
但是你要保证不告诉巴尼
but you got to promise me that you won't tell Barney.
好的 我不告诉他 怎么了?
Fine, I won't tell Barney. What is it?
- 罗宾没有结婚 - 什么?
- Robin's not married. - What?
那她为什么说她结婚了?
Why would she tell me she was?
我不知道 但是我 查遍了加拿大的相关资料
I don't know, but I cross- checked every record in Canada.
没有记录表明她结过婚
There's no record of her ever being married.
这肯定出了问题
There must be some mistake.
我跟你保证 她没有结婚
I promise you. She's not married.
她也不擅长正确泊位
She's not great at parking legally either.
那么是她对我说谎了? 那我该怎么办?
So she lied to me? W--What am I going to do?
我不能和她对证 不能让她知道我把这事说了出去
I-I can't confront her, 'cause then she'll know I told you.
你可以诱导她
You got to lawyer her.
你可以问她一堆问题 把她搞晕
You got to ask her a bunch of questions, try to trip her up,
使她产生罪恶感 不管使什么手段
maybe make her feel guilty, whatever it takes
都要让她自己招供
to get a confession out of her.
谢谢你告诉我你的秘密
Thanks for telling me your secret.
这对我来说 表明了你是多么的...
It means so much to me, that you could be so--
我该怎么措辞?
God, what's the word I'm looking for?
诚实
Honest.
谢谢 泰德
Mm, thanks, Ted.
你知道你最让我感动的是
Yeah. You know what's probably the best part about your honesty?
你竟然这么诚实
How truthful it is.
别这么肉麻了
I say we just move on.
就让我把 "我的女友结婚了"这件事
Well, for me to get total closure on this whole
做一个彻底了断
"my girlfriend has a husband" thing,
我想再稍微地了解清楚一点
I think I might need a little bit more information,
比如说你是几月结婚的?
like what month did you get married?
六月  婚礼是在六月办的
June. We had a June wedding.
六月的加拿大啊
Ah, Canada in June.
真是浪漫
That's the dream.
是宴会还是自助餐会 ??
Sit-down  or buffet?
你要是不记得就很奇怪了
Well, it's... weird that you don't remember.
我只是不知道该如何回答
No, I just didn't know how to answer
因为开胃菜 是在大厅里面吃的
because we did butlered hors d'oeuvres in the atrium,
但宴会实际上 是在餐厅里吃自助餐
but the actual dinner was a buffet in the Food Court
特色菜甜菲力牛排 三文鱼夹心的烤马铃薯卷
featuring a filet mignon or a roasted potato-crusted salmon
还有龙虾蘸白葡萄酒酱
with a lobster scallion beurre blanc.
乐队和司仪?
Band or DJ?
典礼上有管弦四重奏
A string quartet played at the ceremony,
但在宴会上 是个七人乐队伴唱
but for the actual reception, we had a seven-piece band.
我们还专门请了一个萨克斯手
We paid extra for the sax
因为中音萨克斯的 琴声实在很好听
'cause I just love that smooth alto sound.
- 请了几个伴娘? - 7个
- How many bridesmaids? - Seven.
- 花束是? - 杜鹃
- Flowers? - Azaleas.
- 色彩方案? - 偏暗的玫瑰色和黄褐色
- Color scheme? - Dusty rose and sienna.
老公的名字
Husband's name.
- 你没结过婚! - 不 我结了
- You were never married! - Yes, I was.
- 不 你没有 -你怎么知道的?
- No, you weren't. - How do you know?
我在图书馆里查了
I looked it up at the library.
- 那个数据图书馆? - 五楼的第一个
- What library? - The one on Fifth.
- 你什么时候去的? - 今天午饭时候
- When did you go? - Today at lunch,
我点了苹果乾酪和土豆沙拉
and I had an apple brie panini with potato salad...
我不是问你午餐吃的什么
I'm not questioning the lunch part, Ted.
你从哪得到的数据?
What database did you use?
"加拿大商场结婚6000例"
I used the Canadian Mall Marriage 6000.
马修在学校查阅了资料
Fine, Marshall looked it up at school.
- 你告诉马修了?! - 你对我撒了谎!
- You told Marshall?! - You lied to me!
这就是我为什么 不愿意告诉别人秘密的原因
See, this is why I don't tell people secrets.
我把你当成了最能够信任的人
You were supposed to be the one person I trusted the most
你都不能守住秘密
and even you couldn't keep a secret.
但这是一个假秘密
But it was a fake secret.
我只是测试一下你 你是不及格的
Yeah, I was testing you and you failed.
现在你将永远 别想知道我为什么不去商场
And now you're never gonna know why I don't go to the mall.
这样是最好的
And it's good, too.
你在测试我?真难以置信
You  were testing me? That's insane.
是么 难以置信的是 你才知道了多久
Oh, yeah? How long did it take for you to tell Marshall
就把我的秘密告诉了马修? 有五分钟没?
my biggest secret in the world? Five minutes?
- 那根本就不是真的秘密! - 但它也有可能是
- That wasn't a real secret! - Yeah, but it could have been.
你让我要崩裂了!
You are driving me crazy!
难怪你的冒牌丈夫逃去了香港
No wonder your fake husband moved to Hong Kong.
他是因为工作才去的
He moved there for business.
你
You.
没什么事要告诉我么?
You got something to say to me?
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
我知道罗宾根本就没结婚
I know Robin was never really married.
你是怎么知道的?
How could you possibly know that?
然后我就穿上睡裤钻进被窝了
And then I put on my pajamas and got into bed.
你呢?
How about you?
让我想想 我先是乘地铁到学校
Oh, let's see, uh, first I took the subway to school.
吃了个面包
Then I got a bagel.
然后去了图书馆查资料 发现罗宾其实没结婚
Then I went to the library and found out Robin was never married.
受了打击
Crazy.
结果我又饿了 就去了自动售货机那儿
Then I was hungry again, so I went down to the vending machine,
但到我走到那儿时 我又不饿了
but by the time I got down there, I wasn't even hungry anymore.
- 你告诉他了? - 没办法
- You told him? - I had to.
我是这次打赌的监察官
I'm Slap Bet Commissioner.
相信我 我是看在眼里疼在心上
Believe me, this hurts me more than it's gonna hurt you.
废话少说 我在树上 已经练习过好多次了
Don't count on it. I've been practicing on a tree trunk.
- 巴尼要打你三个耳光 - 三个?
- Barney gets three slaps. - Three?
一个是因为你说谎了
还有两个是没得到 我允许就打巴尼的惩罚
One because you lied and two for being prematurely slapped.
一共三个
Three slaps.
但是...
But--
不是吧
Oh, my God.
- 你要哭了? - 哪有
- Are you gonna cry? - No.
你才哭了呢
You're gonna cry.
我认为保守秘密会影响感情发展的
I just don't think it's healthy to keep big secrets in a relationship.
我父母三十年都不怎么沟通
My parents didn't really talk to each other for 30 years
搞得现在离婚了
and now they're divorced.
我是让你更了解我
I have shared more of myself with you
而不是所有人
than I've ever shared with anyone.
就让我留这一个秘密
I'm asking for this one secret,
它对我们的感情不会有影响的
which has nothing to do with us, to just be mine.
我刚接到了一个有趣的电话
So I just got a very interesting phone call.
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
罗宾的秘密我知道
I know Robin's secret.
- 什么? - 没错
- What? - That's right.
我知道了你的秘密 罗宾
I know your secret, Robin.
还是我应该叫你罗宾火花?
Or should I say Robin Sparkles?
你怎么知道这个名字的?
How do you know that name?
因为我知道真相
Because I know the truth,
并且我现在就向你们证明
and I am about to show it to you right now.
过来 泰德 你肯定想知道这个
Gather 'round, Ted, you're gonna want to see this.
我不 不要
Yeah, no, I don't.
什么?
What?
罗宾想保留这个秘密 所以...
Robin wants to keep this a secret, so...
就让它成为秘密吧
it's gonna stay a secret.
它不会一直是秘密的
Yeah, it's not gonna stay a secret.
在我的调查中
You see, in my research,
我认识了某一马来西亚的男子
I came upon a certain gentleman in Malaysia
他有一盘录像带
who is in possession of a certain videotape.
准备在邮件中给我发送过来
He just emailed me that it will be up and running
现在刚好发完
on My Space in about... right now.
罗宾的世界会天翻地覆的
Robin's world is about to be turned upside-down.
我猜的
I mean, I'm guessing.
巴尼 别这样 好么?
Barney, don't, okay?
罗宾 别惊慌
Robin, please don't panic.
我只是想给马修证明我是对的
I'm only gonna show enough to prove to Marshall I was right.
不 巴尼 我说了我们不看
No, Barney, I said we're not watching this.
算了 总有这么一天的
No, it's time.
我很欣慰你愿意这么做
Look, I appreciate what you're trying to do,
但是纸终究包不住火
but if it's out there, there's no point in trying to hide it anymore.
还是面对现实 看看吧
Let's just watch it and be done with it.
你跟我一样觉得紧张么?
Are you as terrified as I am?
我可不想再被打耳光了
I don't want to get slapped again.
我想强调一下 那时我太年轻了
I want to stress that I was young.
可以理解
Yeah, you were.
我不知道怎么做才是好的
And I didn't know any better.
怎么都不会好
They never do.
那刚开始只是单纯的模特工作
And it started out as an innocent modeling job.
都是这么入门的
It always does.
拜托了 约翰逊先生
Please, Mr. Johnson.
我知道是我不好
I'm sorry I was a bad girl.
不要关我禁闭好么
Please don't give me detention.
要不要我做点什么弥补一下?
Isn't there something I can do to make it up to you?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
显而易见  我才是正确的
Well, obviously, I've been proven right,
为了维护罗宾的尊严
so in the interest of Robin's dignity,
演示到此为止
I won't show anymore.
好了 时间不早了 该到行刑时间了
Plus, it's getting late. It's already slap o'clock.
你们在搞什么?
What the hell was that?
我和马修打赌说 你是拍A片的  我赢了
Uh, I slap bet Marshall that you did porn, so I win.
A片? 是就好了 也没这个丢人
Porn? I wish it was porn. It would be less embarrassing.
我知道了
I know.
我为你唱首歌怎样?
How about I sing you a song?
大家一起去商场!
Let's go to the mall, everybody!
我在加拿大是个青春偶像
I was a teenage pop star in Canada.
# Put on your jelly bracelets #
# And your cool graffiti coat #
# At the mall, having fun #
# Is what it's all about #
这是我见过最惊悚的事了
This is the most amazing thing I've ever seen.
- 那是你? - 是
- That's you? - Yes.
我出了张唱片
I had one minor hit.
所以不得不在 全加拿大的商场里作宣传
I had to go all over Canada and sing this song in malls.
整整一年我忙的 只能喝橘子汁吃椒盐卷饼
For a whole year, I lived off of Orange Juliuses and Wetzel's Pretzels.
# Everybody come and play #
# Throw every last care away #
# Let's go to the mall #
# Today #
这是90年代 怎么看起来象80年代
If this is the '90s, why does it look like 1986?
美国93年的时候 加拿大还处在80年代
The '80s didn't come to Canada till, like, '93.
在观看的过程中我要打断一下
Taking a break from the first of many, many viewings,
我肯定这不是A片
I can't help but notice that this isn't porn.
所以  不用请示监察官了
And yet, a slap occurred without the permission
直接执行吧
of the Slap Bet Commissioner.
现在我要 "以其人之道还治其人之身"
Looks like somebody suffered from premature slapulation.
我的天 罗宾还能念rap
Oh, my God, Robin's rapping.
看 她在念rap
Guys, Robin's rapping.
# Went to the mall with # # a couple of friends #
# I had a whole week's # # allowance to spend #
这样  给你两个选择
Okay, I'm going to give you a choice.
要么现在一次打十个耳光
Either ten slaps right now in a row,
要么就是5个耳光 但是场合不限
or five slaps that can be doled out
时间没有截止点
at any point from here to eternity.
你选一次打十个吧
You go with the ten now.
别 不是可以选只挨5个的么?
No way, why get ten when you can get five?
但是你会一直处于 耳光不知何时降临的
Yeah, but the constant fear of knowing that at any moment,
提心吊胆中 会让你精神崩溃的
you could get slapped in the face, would drive you crazy.
我选打5个
I'm going to go with the five for eternity.
- 选的好 - 选错了
- Good call. - Horrible call.
别紧张 哥们 我只是拿我的汽水而已
Relax, dude, I'm just going for my soda, man.
放松点
Take it easy.
别那么搞笑啊
This is going to be fun.
# Let's go to the mall #
# Today #
请问一下
So just to be clear,
你那么想让大家 在今天 去商场?
you wanted everybody to go to the mall today?
我们会反复欣赏这个"经典"的
Wow, we're going to watch this a lot.
简直难以相信 我竟然穿着贝德丝牛仔夹克
I can't believe I ever wore a Bedazzled jean jacket.
那你知道么
Hey, just so you know,
十六岁的我 如果遇见你就会一见钟情
16-year-old me would have been all over you.
而你就是我曾跟别人提起过 在加拿大时的女朋友
You could have been the girlfriend in Canada I told everyone I had.
很抱歉我窥探了这个秘密
Hey, uh, I'm really sorry I pried this out of you.
我应该让它一直埋藏下去的
I probably should have left it alone.
那有什么?
You know what?
你对我更加了解了
You know me better now.
这样不是更好么
That feels kind of nice.
这是第一个
That's one.
# Everybody come and play #
# Throw every last care away #
Wow.
# Let's go to the mall #
# Today #
你是不是每次都得这么笑着唱?
Did you have to laugh like that every time?
是啊
Yes.
# This boy I like #
# Met him at the food court #
# He's got hair like Gretzky #
# And he does jumps # # on his skateboard #
# I hope he asks me out #
# Take me to my favorite spot #
# It'll be just him and me #
# But don't forget the robot #
机器人 嗨!
The robot. Hey!
# But, baby # # I don't want to wait #
# Let's do it #
不  是她迫不及待了
No, she doesn't want to wait.
# I'm gonna rock # # your body anyway #
# I'm gonna rock your # # body till Canada Day #
# Everybody come and play #
# Throw every last care away #
# Let's go to the mall #
# Today, today, today, today #
# Let's go to the ma-a-all #
# Let's go to the mall #
# Today #